<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-US"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.7">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mcint170.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mcint170.github.io//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-US" /><updated>2021-03-10T14:51:34-05:00</updated><id>https://mcint170.github.io//feed.xml</id><title type="html">Brandon McIntyre</title><subtitle>Personal Website</subtitle><author><name>Brandon McIntyre</name></author><entry><title type="html">Inaugural Post</title><link href="https://mcint170.github.io//annoucement/2021/03/09/Inaugural-Post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Inaugural Post" /><published>2021-03-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-03-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://mcint170.github.io//annoucement/2021/03/09/Inaugural-Post</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mcint170.github.io//annoucement/2021/03/09/Inaugural-Post.html">&lt;p&gt;This marks the first offical post on my personal website. If you are seeing this
now, welcome 😃 I hope you find the content here somewhat enjoyable or atleast 
a tad bit interesting. If you are seeing this relatively recently to posting, 
please come back later and I hope to be a little more established here and have more
posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Little Disclaimer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I am just throwing this out here now, please be aware that I am no HTML or Website 
building Guru (well atleast not at this leg in the game). This is my first ever 
dive into HTML / CSS / Jekyll, so if you see some bug, or something is not quite 
right, please feel free to reach out to me and I can try to do my best to address the problem!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;so-whats-my-big-plan&quot;&gt;So what’s my big plan?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My plans are to use this website as a basis for my Personal / Data Science journey.
The hopes is that I can use these posts to show my interests in Data Science and 
Science in general. Hopefully along the way, I can begin to tailor myself as an
expert in some sort of sub-discipline. For now I will remain as open-minded and
free going as I can. If anything, this will be good practice in documenting my
path and act as a centeralized place to express my ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I realize that possibly this could also serve as a place to document posts I create
elsewhere. These could be things like Twitter posts, Medium Posts, LinkedIn posts?
Not really actively posting on any of those platforms currently, but maybe when I grow a little
more confidence in my story telling / article writing skills I will give it a gander?
Well, that is the hope at least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have stuck around to the end of this post thank you! You are very kind and
I hope this gave you some sort of insight into my future plans, thank you for your
time 😊&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Brandon McIntyre</name></author><category term="Annoucement" /><category term="Announcement" /><category term="Special" /><summary type="html">This marks the first offical post on my personal website. If you are seeing this now, welcome 😃 I hope you find the content here somewhat enjoyable or atleast a tad bit interesting. If you are seeing this relatively recently to posting, please come back later and I hope to be a little more established here and have more posts.</summary></entry></feed>